

TRỊNH XUÂN ĐỰC

Front-End Developer

www.trinhxuanduc.info

CONTACT

****** +84967 084 484

trinhxuanduc997@gmail.com

• Thu Dau Mot city

SKILLS

- Web & Mobile Design
- Figma
- Javascript
- Typescript
- ReactJS, NextJs
- Material-UI, Tailwincss...
- Redux, Context APIs
- NodeJS
- ExpressJS
- MongoDB

LANGUAGE

- English (Basic)
- Vietnamese

ABOUT ME

Hi! I'm Duc, a software engineer passionate about programming. I started my career path in my third year of university and have accumulated over 4 years of experience as a Front-End Developer. Additionally, I possess knowledge in UX/UI design. For me, sharing knowledge is highly important. I don't hesitate to face complex problems and challenges in my work and can work under high pressure. Moreover, I'm always ready to learn new programming languages or technology if the job requires it.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end Dev at NTI company

2023- NOW

During my tenure at the company, I worked on an ERP project. The original ERP project had been deployed several years ago and faced issues with performance, functionality, and security. My primary responsibility was to analyze the current system, identify weaknesses and vulnerabilities, and then propose and implement appropriate upgrade solutions. Additionally, I was involved in building new functionalities and share personal knowledge to help the team improve performance at work.

Frelancer 2022 – 2023

 I had the opportunity to work on a project building a Work Management application. The project uses ReactJS, NodeJS, and MongoDB. The web application has main features such as:

- Add, Edit, and Remove tasks for the day. Update the status of the task: todo, doing, done.
- Monthly revenue statistics
- Link Demo:
 - https://workflowmanagementapp.vercel.app/
- Demo account:
 - tk: admin, mk: 123. Select March 2023 to test the Demo.
- I did a personal project about learning English to learn more about NextJS, NodeJS, and MongoDB. The web application has main features such as:
 - o Divide the vocabulary into different courses and topics
 - Learning by flashcards and games to memorize vocabulary
 - Hierarchical vocabulary to review easily
 - Link Demo:
 - https://beelearning.vercel.app/learning/vocabulary/sub jects/
 - Oemo account:
 - tk: ductrinh, mk: 123.
- I also devoted most of my time to improving my English language skills.

TRINH XUÂN ĐỰC Front-End Developer

Front-end Dev at ISOL company

2019 - 2022

- I had the opportunity to work on an ERP project with many modules such as HR, Sales, Accounting, and so on.
- I'm responsible for working directly with the project in progress for the client. I collaborate with the designer to get the feature requirements and Back-End Dev to resolve the project's problems. Some of the features I implemented include exporting and importing Excel, printing, and exporting pdf, besides there are basic features such as adding, editing, removing, and calling API to update data
- Join the discussion to clarify what business will be deployed on the web application. There are several modules and feature pages I have been involved in, for instance, the Approval module, Expenditure page of the Accounting module, Customer Purchase Order page, Price Management page of the Sale module, etc.

EDUCATION

THU DAU MOT UNIVERSITY

2016 - 2020

Graduated in Software Engineering

Udemy In 2024

UX/UI design

Certificate: https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-

996a9daa-c214-4f8c-b6df-34fc16438dca

REFERENCES

Nguyễn Lê Thanh Trúc

Team leader FE at ISOL company

Phone: 0366101984

Email: nlthanhtruc9794@gmail.com

Nguyễn Tiến Phúc

Team leader at NTI company

Phone: 0868 844 812

Email: phucnguyen090895@gmail.com